[
  {
    "question": "What does a Python say when it's scared?",
    "answer": "hiss-terical"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did the programmer quit his job?",
    "answer": "Because he didn't get arrays"
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s a function’s favorite dance move?",
    "answer": "the return"
  },
  {
    "question": "What's a loop's favorite music genre?",
    "answer": "infinite jazz"
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s the object-oriented way to become wealthy?",
    "answer": "Inheritance"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why was the JavaScript developer sad?",
    "answer": "Because he didn’t know how to 'null' his feelings"
  },
  {
    "question": "What did the array say to the linked list?",
    "answer": "I'm more direct"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did the Python file go to therapy?",
    "answer": "Too many unresolved imports"
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s a coder’s favorite pickup line?",
    "answer": "You had me at Hello World"
  },
  {
    "question": "Why can’t you trust while loops?",
    "answer": "They might never end"
  }
]
